A Guide to the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial records FA061
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1917-1949; 3
  - Appropriations - Social Studies, 3_06
    - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Reports (Box 75, Folder 794)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Reports (Box 75, Folder 795)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Reports (Box 76, Folder 796)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Reports (Box 76, Folder 797)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Reports (Box 76, Folder 798)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Reports (Box 76, Folder 799)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Reports (Box 76, Folder 800)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Wharton School - Reports (Box 76, Folder 801)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1923-1925 (Box 77, Folder 802)
    - University of South Africa, 1927 (Box 77, Folder 803)
    - University of Stockholm - Social Science Institute, 1924-1929 (Box 77, Folder 804)
      Training of social workers; research center in social economics.
    - University of Texas, 1926-1932 (Box 77, Folder 805)
      LSRM-RF. Development of social science program; Bureau of Business Research. Walter Splawn.
    - University of Texas, 1926-1932 (Box 77, Folder 806)
    - University of Texas - Reports (Box 77, Folder 807)
    - University of Texas - Reports (Box 77, Folder 808)
    - University of Texas - Pamphlets (Box 77, Folder 809)
    - University of Vermont - Eugenics Survey, 1927-1931 (Box 77, Folder 810)
      LSRM-RF. Social welfare and rural research. Vermont Commission on Country Life.
    - University of Vermont - Eugenics Survey - Reports (Box 77, Folder 811)
    - University of Virginia, 1925-1931 (Box 78, Folder 812)
      LSRM-RF. Research, professorships; model after Institute of Public Affairs at North Carolina. Wilson Gee, Edwin Alderman.
    - University of Virginia, 1925-1931 (Box 78, Folder 813)
    - University of Virginia - Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 78, Folder 814)
    - Vanderbilt University - Endowment of Social Sciences, 1925-1941 (Box 78, Folder 815)
    - Vanderbilt University - Endowment of Social Sciences, 1925-1941 (Box 78, Folder 816)
    - Vanderbilt University - Endowment of Social Sciences, 1925-1941 (Box 78, Folder 817)
    - Vienna National Library, 1926 (Box 78, Folder 818)
    - Washington University - School of Social Work, 1927-1929 (Box 78, Folder 819)
    - Western Reserve University - School of Applied Social Science - Pamphlets (Box 78, Folder 820)
    - Winsor, Max, 1926-1928 (Box 78, Folder 821)
      Special crime studies, Lawrence B. Dunham, Arthur Woods.
    - Woodworth, R. S., 1927-1929 (Box 78, Folder 822)
    - Yale University, 1924-1929 (Box 79, Folder 823)
    - Yale University - Reports (Box 79, Folder 824)
    - Yale University Press, 1924-1926 (Box 79, Folder 825)
    - Yale University - Institute of Human Behavior, 1928-1929 (Box 79, Folder 826)
    - Yale University - Institute of Psychology, 1922-1929 (Box 79, Folder 827)
      Research and graduate instruction.
    - Yale University - Institute of Psychology, 1922-1929 (Box 79, Folder 828)
    - Yale University - Institute of Psychology - Pamphlets (Box 79, Folder 829)
    - Yale University - Law School, 1926-1938 (Box 79, Folder 830)
      LSRM-RF. Research in Law Administration. Charles E. Clark.
    - Yale University - Law School, 1926-1938 (Box 79, Folder 831)
    - Yale University - Law School - Pamphlets (Box 79, Folder 832)
    - Yale University - Law School Credit Study, 1928 (Box 80, Folder 833)
    - Yenching University - Division of Social Sciences, 1928-1939 (Box 80, Folder 834)
      LSRM-RF. Development of departments. Peiping, Olin Wannamaker.
    - Yenching University - Division of Social Sciences, 1928-1939 (Box 80, Folder 835)
    - Yenching University - Division of Social Sciences, 1928-1939 (Box 80, Folder 836)
    - Yenching University - Division of Social Sciences - Pamphlets (Box 80, Folder 837)
    - Yenching University - Division of Social Sciences - Reports (Box 80, Folder 838)
  - Appropriations - Social Welfare, 3_07
    - Alta Social Settlement, 1917-1925 (Box 81, Folder 839)
      Assimilate and Americanize Italian immigrants through clubs, entertainments, health education, recreation. Taken over by Welfare Federation of Cleveland. Harry Sims.
    - American Association of Social Workers, 1922-1926 (Box 81, Folder 840)
      Standards, broaden program.
    - American Association of Social Workers - Publication, 1926 (Box 81, Folder 841)
    - American Foundation for the Blind, 1924-1928 (Box 81, Folder 842)
      Endowment and general background information, special projects.
    - Association for Improving the Conditions of the Poor, 1919-1929 (Box 81, Folder 843)
      Originally the New York Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor. General background information, Italian district community work. Arthur Milbank.
    - Backyard Playground Association, 1923-1924 (Box 81, Folder 844)
      New York City. Playground equipment.
    - Better Homes in America, 1923-1930 (Box 81, Folder 845)
      Housing corporation to lessen shortage; general background information, Herbert Hoover. Christian Herter.
    - Better Homes in America, 1923-1930 (Box 81, Folder 846)
    - Big Brother - Big Sister Federation, 1921-1924 (Box 81, Folder 847)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities, 1919-1929 (Box 81, Folder 848)
    - Brooklyn Federation of Jewish Charities, 1919-1922 (Box 81, Folder 849)
    - Bureau of Part Time Work, 1923-1926 (Box 81, Folder 850)
      New York City. Advisory Committee. Incorporating.
    - Charity Organization Society, 1919-1929 (Box 81, Folder 851)
      New York City. General background information.
    - Children's Aid Society, 1920 (Box 81, Folder 852)
    - Children's Village, 1926-1927 (Box 81, Folder 853)
      Located in Dobbs Ferry, New York. National Training School for Institution Executives and Clinic.
    - Children's Village, 1928 (Box 82, Folder 854)
      Located in Dobbs Ferry, New York.
    - Children's Welfare Federation, 1923-1929 (Box 82, Folder 855)
    - Cleveland Community Fund, 1919-1928 (Box 82, Folder 856)
      For Welfare Federation of Cleveland; Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA), general background information.
    - Council on Adult Education for the Foreign Born, 1922-1928 (Box 82, Folder 857)
    - Council on Adult Education for the Foreign Born, 1922-1928 (Box 82, Folder 858)
    - Hope Farm, 1923-1925 (Box 82, Folder 859)
      Dutchess County, New York. Advisory Committee. Community for children resulting from destitution or improper guardianship.
    - Housing Situation in New York City, 1923-1924 (Box 82, Folder 860)
      Advisory Committee. Limited dividend housing corporation to acquire land and housing and develop garden cities. City Housing Corporation. Alexander Bing.
      Photographs of the City Housing Corporation were removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 3, Folder 24.
    - Institute for Crippled and Disabled Men, 1923-1926 (Box 82, Folder 861)
      Survey, extension, clearinghouse. Efforts in New York City and nationally.
    - Legal Aid Society, 1919-1922 (Box 82, Folder 862)
    - National Association for the Legal Aid Organizations, 1925-1929 (Box 82, Folder 863)
      LSRM-RF. General background information; editorial work of "annals"; handbook of standard procedure, handbook of common law.
    - National Association of Travelers Aid Societies, 1919-1924 (Box 82, Folder 864)
    - National Association of Travelers Aid Societies, 1919-1924 (Box 82, Folder 865)
    - National Association of Travelers Aid Societies, 1925-1928 (Box 83, Folder 866)
    - National Association of Travelers Aid Societies, 1925-1928 (Box 83, Folder 867)
    - National Association of Travelers Aid Societies - Reports (Box 83, Folder 868)
    - National Catholic Service School, 1923-1930 (Box 83, Folder 869)
      LSRM-RF. Training Catholic women as social workers and offering opportunity for leadership in Catholic women's organizations, general background information.
    - National Catholic Service School, 1923-1930 (Box 83, Folder 870)
    - National Child Labor Committee, 1922-1923 (Box 83, Folder 871)
    - National Committee on Legal Aid Work, 1924-1927 (Box 83, Folder 872)
      Advisory Committee-LSRM. Study of the Administration of legal justice in the United States.
    - National Committee on Social Work, 1922-1929 (Box 83, Folder 873)
      Toward its conference.
    - National Consumers League, 1923 (Box 83, Folder 874)
    - National Council for Women, 1925 (Box 83, Folder 875)
    - National Fire Protection Association, 1928 (Box 83, Folder 876)
    - National Social Work Council, 1922-1932 (Box 83, Folder 877)
      LSRM-RF. Heads of national organizations to promote better understanding, pool experiences. General background information. H. S. Brancher. David Holbrook.
    - National Social Work Council, 1922-1932 (Box 83, Folder 878)
    - National Society on Penal Information, 1922-1930 (Box 83, Folder 879)
      Survey of medical conditions in Federal and State Prisons.
    - National Women's Party, 1922 (Box 84, Folder 880)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association, 1921-1930 (Box 84, Folder 881)
      LSRM-RF. Education for immigrant women - home and neighborhood classes in English. General background information, (Emergency Committee on the Education of non-English Speaking Women.) Elizabeth Woodward.
      Photographs removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 3, Folder 23.
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association, 1921-1930 (Box 84, Folder 882)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association, 1921-1930 (Box 84, Folder 883)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association, 1921-1930 (Box 84, Folder 884)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association, 1921-1930 (Box 84, Folder 885)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association, 1921-1930 (Box 84, Folder 886)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association, 1921-1930 (Box 84, Folder 887)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association - Reports (Box 84, Folder 888)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association - Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 84, Folder 889)
    - Neighborhood Teacher's Association - Maps and Charts (Box 84, Folder 890, Folder 1)
    - New York Community Trust, 1923-1931 (Box 85, Folder 891)
    - New York Community Trust - Reports and Pamphlets (Box 85, Folder 892)
    - New York Probation and Protective Association, 1922 (Box 85, Folder 893)
    - New York Society for Experimental Study of Education, 1927-1931 (Box 85, Folder 894)
      LSRM-RF. Adult education of illiterates; provide primary adult teaching materials.
    - New York Travelers Aid Society, 1919-1927 (Box 85, Folder 895)
      Extension at the docks. Guide service for immigrants. General background information.
    - New York Travelers Aid Society, 1919-1927 (Box 85, Folder 896)
    - New York Travelers Aid Society, 1919-1927 (Box 85, Folder 897)
    - People's Institute, 1919-1920 (Box 85, Folder 898)
      New York City. General background information, music league, concerts, forums, community center work, night school.
      Photographs removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 3, Folder 25.
    - People's Institute, 1921-1929 (Box 86, Folder 899)
    - People's Institute, 1921-1929 (Box 86, Folder 900)
    - People's Institute - Reports (Box 86, Folder 901)
    - President's Conference on Unemployment, 1923-1930 (Box 86, Folder 902)
      LSRM-RF. Emergency and preventative measures. E. E. Hunt, Herbert Hoover.
    - President's Conference on Unemployment, 1923-1930 (Box 86, Folder 903)
    - Salvation Army, 1919-1929 (Box 86, Folder 904)
      General background information, training college; home service.
    - Salvation Army, 1919-1929 (Box 86, Folder 905)
    - Social Welfare and Public Administration - Europe, 1928-1929 (Box 86, Folder 906)
      S. H. Walker Study.
    - Social Welfare and Public Administration - Europe - Pamphlets (Box 86, Folder 907)
    - Social Work - Pamphlets (Box 86, Folder 908)
    - Southern Cooperative League, 1920-1921 (Box 87, Folder 909)
    - State Bureau of Public Welfare - Virginia, 1927-1930 (Box 87, Folder 910)
      LSRM-RF. Strengthen central administration and research staff. Frank Bane.
    - State Charities Aid Association, 1920-1931 (Box 87, Folder 911)
      LSRM-RF. Survey and analysis of placing children in foster homes; general background information; develop child caring work on a county basis in New York; work in mental hygiene, public health. Homer Folks.
    - State Charities Aid Association, 1920-1931 (Box 87, Folder 912)
    - State Charities Aid Association, 1920-1931 (Box 87, Folder 913)
    - State Charities Aid Association, 1920-1931 (Box 87, Folder 914)
    - State Charities Aid Association, 1920-1931 (Box 87, Folder 915)
    - State Charities Aid Association, 1920-1931 (Box 87, Folder 916)
    - State Charities Aid Association - Mental Hygiene, 1925-1926 (Box 88, Folder 917)
      Statistical study of records of mental disease of the New York State Hospital Commission.
    - State Charities Aid Association - Reports (Box 88, Folder 918)
    - State Charities Aid Association - Reports (Box 88, Folder 919)
    - State Charities Aid Association - Reports (Box 88, Folder 920)
    - State Charities Aid Association - Reports (Box 88, Folder 921)
    - Summer Camps and Convalescent Homes - Chart (Box 88, Folder 922)
    - United Neighborhood Homes of New York, 1922-1924 (Box 88, Folder 923)
    - University of Nevada, 1925 (Box 88, Folder 924)
    - Vocational Guidance, 1926 (Box 88, Folder 925)
    - Vocational Service for Juniors, 1923-1936 (Box 89, Folder 926)
      Counselling, placement, training program for counselors; general background information.
    - Vocational Service for Juniors, 1923-1936 (Box 89, Folder 927)
    - Vocational Service for Juniors, 1923-1936 (Box 89, Folder 928)
    - Vocational Service for Juniors - Reports (Box 89, Folder 929)
    - Welfare Camp, 1925-1926 (Box 89, Folder 930)
      New York City. For children with venereal disease.
    - Welfare Council, 1926-1935 (Box 89, Folder 931)
      LSRM-RF. New York City. Cooperation and coordination of charitable and social work; research and fact findings. William Hodson, Homer Folks.
    - Welfare Council, 1926-1935 (Box 89, Folder 932)
    - Welfare Council, 1926-1935 (Box 89, Folder 933)
    - Welfare Council - Homeless Men, 1928-1929 (Box 89, Folder 934)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 90, Folder 935)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 90, Folder 936)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 90, Folder 937)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 90, Folder 938)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 91, Folder 939)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 91, Folder 940)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 91, Folder 941)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 91, Folder 942)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 91, Folder 943)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 92, Folder 944)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 92, Folder 945)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 92, Folder 946)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 92, Folder 947)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 93, Folder 948)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 93, Folder 949)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 93, Folder 950)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 93, Folder 951)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 93, Folder 952)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 94, Folder 953)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 94, Folder 954)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 94, Folder 955)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 94, Folder 956)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 94, Folder 957)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 94, Folder 958)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 95, Folder 959)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 95, Folder 960)
    - Welfare Council - Reports (Box 95, Folder 961)
    - Welfare Council - Pamphlets (Box 95, Folder 962)
    - Welfare Federation of Cleveland, 1919-1922 (Box 95, Folder 963)
      General background information, Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA).
    - Women's Cooperative Alliance, 1923 (Box 95, Folder 964)
    - Women's Educational-Industrial Alliance, 1921-1928 (Box 95, Folder 965)
      Boston. Social and industrial advancement of women.
  - Appropriations - Interracial Relations, 3_08
    - Association for the Study of Negro Life and History, 1921-1929 (Box 96, Folder 966)
      LSRM-RF. Journal of Negro History, special studies, Carter Woodson, William E. Dodd, Arthur Schlesinger.
    - Association for the Study of Negro Life and History, 1921-1929 (Box 96, Folder 967)
    - Association for the Study of Negro Life and History - Reports (Box 96, Folder 968)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Negro, 1925-1931 (Box 96, Folder 969)
      LSRM-RF. Organizations of troops, scout work among racial groups.
      Photographs removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 3, Folder 26.
    - Boy Scouts of America - Negro, 1925-1931 (Box 96, Folder 970)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Negro, 1925-1931 (Box 96, Folder 971)
    - Brooklyn Urban League, 1926 (Box 96, Folder 972)
    - Brown University - Study of Ethnic Factors, 1925-1927 (Box 96, Folder 973)
      Racial forces in community life. Problems of races and nationalities. Construct a practical program.
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, 1921-1932 (Box 96, Folder 974)
      LSRM-RF. General background information. Main southern organization in this work.
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, 1921-1932 (Box 96, Folder 975)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, 1921-1932 (Box 96, Folder 976)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation - Pamphlets (Box 97, Folder 977)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation - Pamphlets (Box 97, Folder 978)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation - Reports (Box 97, Folder 979)
    - Commission on Interracial Cooperation - Reports (Box 97, Folder 980)
    - Durham Conference, 1928-1931 (Box 97, Folder 981)
      LSRM-RF. Facts of progress and apply possible remedies through existing organizations.
    - Durham Conference, 1928-1931 (Box 97, Folder 982)
    - Durham Conference - Pamphlets (Box 97, Folder 983)
    - Fellowships, 1926-1945 (Box 97, Folder 984)
    - Fellowship - Beckham, 1928 (Box 97, Folder 985)
    - Fellowship - Blooah, 1927-1932 (Box 97, Folder 986)
    - Fellowship - Carrington, 1928-1929 (Box 98, Folder 987)
    - Fellowship - Chivers, 1927-1928 (Box 98, Folder 988)
    - Fellowship - Cresswell, 1928 (Box 98, Folder 989)
    - Fellowship - Davis, 1927 (Box 98, Folder 990)
    - Fellowship - Dunham, 1928-1931 (Box 98, Folder 991)
    - Fellowship - Frazier, 1927-1928 (Box 98, Folder 992)
    - Fellowship - King, 1927-1928 (Box 98, Folder 993)
    - Fellowship - Taylor, 1927-1928 (Box 98, Folder 994)
    - Fellowship - Whiting, 1927-1928 (Box 98, Folder 995)
    - Interracial Relations - Policy (Box 98, Folder 996)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1928 (Box 98, Folder 997)
    - National Interracial Conference, 1927-1928 (Box 98, Folder 998)
    - National Interracial Conference - Reports (Box 98, Folder 999)
    - National Interracial Conference - Reports (Box 98, Folder 1000)
    - National Interracial Conference - Reports (Box 98, Folder 1001)
    - National Negro Business League, 1926-1930 (Box 99, Folder 1002)
      LSRM-SF. Survey of Negro business in United States. Robert R. Moton.
    - National Negro Business League, 1926-1930 (Box 99, Folder 1003)
    - National Negro Business League, 1926-1930 (Box 99, Folder 1004)
    - National Urban League, 1918-1933 (Box 99, Folder 1005)
      LSRM-SF. General background information. Eugene K. Jones, L. Hollingsworth Jones.
    - National Urban League, 1918-1933 (Box 99, Folder 1006)
    - National Urban League, 1918-1933 (Box 99, Folder 1007)
    - National Urban League, 1918-1933 (Box 99, Folder 1008)
    - National Urban League, 1918-1933 (Box 99, Folder 1009)
    - National Urban League, 1918-1933 (Box 99, Folder 1010)
    - National Urban League, 1934-1938 (Box 100, Folder 1011)
    - National Urban League - Pamphlet (Box 100, Folder 1012)
    - National Urban League - Reports (Box 100, Folder 1013)
    - National Urban League - Reports (Box 100, Folder 1014)
    - "Negro in America", 1925-1926 (Box 100, Folder 1015)
      Leonard Outhwaite Study.
    - Negro Education - Dongall Report, 1924-1926 (Box 100, Folder 1016)
      Fellowship.
    - Negro Health, 1925-1928 (Box 100, Folder 1017)
      Photographs removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 3, Folder 27.
    - Negro Legal Status Survey - Houston, 1927-1930 (Box 101, Folder 1018)
      Legal justice; status and activities of Negro lawyers.
    - Negro Legal Status Survey - Houston - Reports (Box 101, Folder 1019)
    - Negro Problems, 1925-1929 (Box 101, Folder 1020)
    - Negro Problems, 1925-1929 (Box 101, Folder 1021)
    - Negro Problems - Reports (Box 101, Folder 1022)
    - Negro Problems Conference, 1927-1928 (Box 101, Folder 1023)
      New Haven.
    - Negro Problems Conference - Report (Box 102, Folder 1024)
    - Negro Study - Africa, 1925-1926 (Box 102, Folder 1025)
    - Negro Survey - Coahoma County, 1924-1926 (Box 102, Folder 1026)
      Leo M. Forest, T. J. Woofter.
    - Negro Yearbook, 1925 (Box 102, Folder 1027)
    - Negro - Miscellaneous, 1923-1928 (Box 102, Folder 1028)
    - New York Urban League, 1920-1928 (Box 102, Folder 1029)
      Industrial work. Employment and vocational guidance. Health and housing. Labor adjustments. Elizabeth Walton.
    - New York Urban League, 1920-1928 (Box 102, Folder 1030)
    - New York Urban League, 1920-1928 (Box 102, Folder 1031)
    - North Carolina State Board of Charities - Negro Welfare, 1927-1929 (Box 102, Folder 1032)
      LSRM-SF. Study of Negro life and social problems. Program to develop leadership, training, education. Kate Burr Johnson.
    - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1924-1928 (Box 103, Folder 1033)
      Training of visiting teachers for improvement of village schools in Africa. Anson Phelps Stokes, Thomas Jesse Jones.
    - Pittsburgh Federation - Child Conservation League, 1926 (Box 103, Folder 1034)
    - Ross, Frank - Southern Trip, 1925 (Box 103, Folder 1035)
      Conditions of Negro Migration.
    - Spelman College, 1927-1930 (Box 103, Folder 1036)
      LSRM-SF. Fund to promote physical, mental, social, and spiritual well being of young Negro women, nursery school and lab. Florence M. Read.
    - Standard Life Insurance, 1924 (Box 103, Folder 1037)
      Service company selling land to Negros at a rate so that they can afford to buy and build homes.
    - Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute, 1924-1928 (Box 103, Folder 1038)
      Department of Records and Research; statistical and social information about Negro life in America. Robert R. Moton, Monroe N. Work.
    - University of North Carolina - Negro Studies, 1925-1928 (Box 103, Folder 1039)
      Special studies. Howard Odum.
    - University of North Carolina - Negro Studies, 1925-1928 (Box 103, Folder 1040)
    - University of North Carolina - Negro Studies, 1925-1928 (Box 103, Folder 1041)
    - University of North Carolina - Negro Studies - Report (Box 103, Folder 1042)
    - Young Mens Christian Association Graduate School - Interracial Library, 1928-1932 (Box 103, Folder 1043)
      LSRM-SF. Nashville, at Fisk University.
  - Appropriations - General Education, 3_09
    - American Council on Education, 1924-1927 (Box 104, Folder 1044)
    - American Council on Education - Handbook, 1925-1928 (Box 104, Folder 1045)
      American Universities and Colleges.
    - American Council on Education - International Education, 1923-1928 (Box 104, Folder 1046)
      Merger of American Council on Education with American Universities Union. Development of an International Institute of Education. C. R. Mann.